Would you stop it!
(Howard:)Now, listen to me.
(Howard:)There's a welcome party
for incoming post-docs tonight.
(Howard:)Go to it and meet someone
who isn't made of grease or pie.
(Raj:)You think you're so cool
because your wife is a person?
(Howard:)Look, Bernie's at a neuroscience
conference with Amy.
(Howard:)-I'll go with you.
-You would do that for me?
(Howard:)Of course. You're my friend.
I want you to be happy.
(Raj:)Thanks.
(Raj:)Oh, Sheldon, since Amy's out of town,
would you like to join us?
(Sheldon:)I want you to be happy, too,
(Sheldon:)but not enough
to do anything about it.
(Bernadette(on phone):)Howie, stop. I can't talk like that.
Amy's right here.
(Amy(on phone):)Sheldon, stop. For the last time,
I will not bring home bed bugs.
(Bernadette:)The hotel's nice.
There's a pool, a gym,
(Bernadette:)the bar looks like fun.
(Amy:)Because I looked in the bed,
and there are no bugs.